saintlad.com 2019-06-17

# Privacy Policy

#### The Saint Privacy Policy was updated on 8th August, 2018.

The privacy of registered and unregistered users (“users” or “you”) is very important to us. This Privacy Policy intends to describe: what type of information we collect; how we use, share, and guard the information and your choices regarding your use of the Saintlad.com website and services (the “Website”).

### Information We Collect

You may choose to provide us with general or specific information about yourself when using the Website, including a user name and email address. Also, we may collect web surfing data such as your IP address, server log data, cookie information, areas of the Website you have visited, and if you clicked on advertisements. We use different types of technologies to collect this information, including cookies and single-pixel GIFs.

If your browser is configured to accept the cookies, these cookies will be used to recognize your computer when you visit the Website to allow us to provide updates regarding the Website, to learn how you use the Website so that we can develop new services, and to show you advertisements. You can configure your browser to block cookies; however, if you do, the Website may not function properly or at all.

You may also provide us with personal information. For example, if you choose to register at the Website, you will be asked to create a username and provide a valid email address. If you upload, post, or distribute to the Website information, data, text, photos, audio, links, video, images, graphics, or other content or materials of any nature (collectively, “User Submissions”), those User Submissions, along with your username or other information, may be provided to other users. To limit the amount of personal information disclosed you may consider providing a username other than your actual name.

### Use and Sharing of Collected Information

We may use non-personally identifiable information collected to improve the quality of the Website; for example, to diagnose problems, assess and maintain security, place ad on webpages receiving more web traffic, and allow you to log in or access your profile information automatically. We may use non-personally identifiable information to determine user demographics, interests, and behavior and may market the Website by sharing non-personally identifiable information with advertisers and other partners. We also may provide your non-personally identifiable information to contractors so that they can perform services for us.

We use information you provide to: (1) handle or respond to inquiries you initiate with us (such as a customer service request or job application); (2) communicate information that we believe to be of interest to you via email; (3) improve our products and services; (4) fulfill your requests to share information you find on the Website with friends/other parties you have designated; (5) identify relevant advertisements to display. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may use your information to notify you of important changes to the Website, new services, and special offers. If you do not want to receive such notices, you may opt out as instructed in the Saint Terms of Use. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding sales, updates, improvements, or special offers; provided, however that you may not opt-out of receiving notices required by applicable law via email and you hereby agree that our electronic signature on such notices is adequate. If we have provided any third party with your personal information at your election or request, you will have to contact the third-party directly with any opt-out request. If we provide any of the information collected from you with a third party at your election or request, their use of that information will be governed by their privacy policy.

As the Service provides social functions, we may allow other users to access certain information you provide, such as profile information, your User Submissions, videos you have viewed, and subjects you are interested in. In addition, we allow RSS syndication of all public Service content.

We may release information, in our sole discretion, in response to the law, a court order, law enforcement request, or investigation or to protect our rights, property, or other interests, including those of our customers or other third parties or to prevent illegal activities or violations of the Saint Terms of Use.

In the event that we, in whole or in part, establish a partnership with another company, or are acquired by or merged with another company, collected information may be transferred to the partner or the acquiring or merging company.

### Changing and Deleting

You can access your personal information through your profile on the Website and delete, change or correct information; however, Saint cannot guarantee that all copies of such information will be immediately deleted from its servers.

### Child Protection

We do not offer the Website to, or target, persons under the age of 13. In compliance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, any information we receive from people we believe to be under 13 will be purged from our database.

### Security

We use industry standard security measures to protect against collected information. However, the Internet is not 100% secure and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

### Links to Advertisers and Other Websites

Advertisements and links to third-party advertisers may be displayed on the Website or emailed to you. Third-party ad servers use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Website. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content. Saint does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Saint to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. In addition, third-party advertisers may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here and here. The information advertisers or other third parties collect is governed by their privacy policies, not by this Privacy Policy. In addition, User Submissions may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web publishers, advertisers, or other websites that may be linked to the Website.

### Acceptance of Privacy Policy

By using the Website, you are accepting the then-current Privacy Policy, which may be updated from time to time. Any changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted here and are effective upon posting.

### Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please contact us **[here](https://www.saintlad.com/contact-saint/)**.
